[["'s", 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['da', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['straight', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['stadium', 'I-LOC', 'O'], ['stadium', 'I-LOC', 'O'], ['dello', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['w', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['floating', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['sans', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['van', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['for', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['a', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['need', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['the', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['for', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['meeting', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['the', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['for', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ["'s", 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['shepherds', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['cocker', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['spaniels', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['the', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['products', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-LOC', 'O'], ['and', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['of', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['on', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['and', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['and', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['and', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ["'s", 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['cup', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['premier', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['league', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['league', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['of', 'I-LOC', 'O']]