[['L.', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['F.A.', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['F.A.', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['F.A.', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['F.A.', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['9.4-0-43-1', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['B.', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['1.', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Ltd.', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['N.', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['W46.50', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['W97.50', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['N.M.', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['N.M.', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Russian-U.S.', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Russian-U.S.', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['ST.', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['St.', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['St.', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['St.', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['.', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['A.M.', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['A.M.', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['U.S.', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['U.S.', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['N.M.', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['N.M.', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['K.T.', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['K.T.', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['I.D.E.A', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['I.D.E.A', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['I.D.E.A', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['then-U.S.', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['then-U.S.', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['N.IRELAND', 'B-LOC', 'O']]