[['Uzbekistan', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Uzbek', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Asian', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Uzbekistan', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Hiroshige', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Defender', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Hassan', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Bitar', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Hosts', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Marcello', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Corrado', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['World', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Dominguez', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Nicola', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Mazzucato', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Asian', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Defender', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Hassan', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Kazuyoshi', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Takagi', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Bitar', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Miura', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Naoki', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Honda', 'I-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Louay', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Asian', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Uzbekistan', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Uzbekistan', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Japan', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Syria', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['China', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Inzamamul', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Shahid', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Saqlain', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Doull', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['New', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Challenge', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Cup', 'B-MISC', 'I-MISC'], ['Blinker', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Wednesday', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Blinker', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Engllsh', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bowyer', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Bowyer', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Yorkshire', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Milan', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Tel', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Spor', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Bologna', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Zagreb', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Berlin', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Panathinaikos', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Efes', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Pilsen', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Belgrade', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Bologna', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Little', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Queenslander', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Campese', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Barbarians', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Twickenham', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['All', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Black', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Barbarians', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Pontypridd', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Burke', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Zimbabwe', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Chapman', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Golf', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['Club', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['South', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Hennie', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Botes', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Whitelaw', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Anghel', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Stefan', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Iordanescu', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Steaua', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['European', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Steaua', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Stefan', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Goias', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Blewett', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Lara', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Lloyd', 'I-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Shivnarine', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Chanderpaul', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Moody', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Moody', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Moody', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Moody', 'I-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Ambrose', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Cricket', 'I-LOC', 'O'], ['Ground', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Sheffield', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Shield', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Victoria', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Cricket', 'I-LOC', 'O'], ['Ground', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Tour', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Lloyd', 'I-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Lloyd', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Sydney', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Cricket', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Ground', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Ground', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Junior', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Chen', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Indra', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Sun', 'B-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Jun', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Budi', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Indra', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Wijaya', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Sun', 'B-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Jun', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Allan', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Ye', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Camilla', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Susi', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Camilla', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Gong', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['National', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Arab', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Aly', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['League', 'B-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Ny', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Islanders', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['League', 'B-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Hartford', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Islanders', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Bay', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Indianapolis', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Colts', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Indianapolis', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Cincinnati', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Philadelphia', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['East', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Dallas', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Cowboys', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Washington', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Redskins', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Jets', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Arizona', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Green', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Bay', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Packers', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Quentin', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Kerwin', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Marvin', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Harrison', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Philadelphia', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Eagles', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Ty', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Basketball', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['League', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Football', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['League', 'B-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['Ohio', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['State', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Lombardi', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Award', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Houston', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Pace', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Ohio', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['State', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Rose', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Arizona', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['State', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Pace', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Pace', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Virginia', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Tech', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Cornell', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Arizona', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['State', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Jared', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Nebraska', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Lombardi', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Award', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Green', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Bay', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Packers', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Gourvennec', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Paris', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Starbuck', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Paris', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Bormirow', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Karlsruhe', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Dundee', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Freiburg', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Costa', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Oviedo', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Salamanca', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Glasgow', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Correct', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Double', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Davor', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pedrag', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Raul', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Victor', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Guillermo', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Amor', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Manolo', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Gheorghe', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Popescu', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Enrique', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Ferrer', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Chendo', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Real', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Madrid-Barcelona', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Madrid', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bilbao', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Vallecano', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Vigo', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Espanyol', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Gijon', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Sport', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Costa', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Fair', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Play', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Costa', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Weah', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Costa', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Costa', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Costa', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Weah', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Weah', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Europoean', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Serie', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Bologna', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Igor', 'B-PER', 'I-MISC'], ['Bologna', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Bottom', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Fausto', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Lazio', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Roma', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Poor', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Lazio', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Champions', 'B-MISC', 'I-MISC'], ['Napoli', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Verona', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Verona', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Alen', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Vicenza', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Vicenza', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Uruguayan', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Charleroi', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Charleroi', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Belgrade', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Bologna', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Kinder', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['World', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Mahindra', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['International', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Eyles', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Mahindra', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['International', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Nicol', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Eyles', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Zulu', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['African', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['National', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Izingolweni', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Zulu', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Mangosuthu', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Inkatha', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['State', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['State', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Communist', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Albright', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Communists', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Fronta', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Dnes', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Czechs', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Radio', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Social', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Hungarian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Democratic', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Oradea', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Sibiu', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Czech', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Democratic', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Modernisation', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Brno', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Zieleniec', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Social', 'B-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Holocaust', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Democrats', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Piwowarskie', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Zywcu', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Boxmeer', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Heineken', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Carlsberg', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Okocim', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['South', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['African', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Breweries', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Tychy', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Brewpole', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Elbrewery', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Company', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Ltd.', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Boxmeer', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Czech', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Okocim', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Carlsberg', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Heineken', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Full', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Light', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Boxmeer', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Heineken', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Zywiec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Department', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Tambang', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Timah', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Timah', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Receipt', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Telkom', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Indonesia', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Telkom', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Ireland', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Irish', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Republican', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['British', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['American', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Monopolies', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Mergers', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Trade', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Office', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Fair', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Trading', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Airways-American', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['British', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['American', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Heathrow', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['American', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['British', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['British', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['British', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['American', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['London', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Worth', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Office', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Fair', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Trade', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['British', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['American', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Office', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Fair', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Trading', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Mediterranean', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Med', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Low', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Med', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Sale', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Grammar', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['School', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Manchester', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Street', 'I-LOC', 'O'], ['Gorst', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Gorst', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Electronic', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Information', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Private', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Initiative', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Oceanic', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Control', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Centre', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Australia-West', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Indies', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Manitoba', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Manitoba', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Cwt', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Manitoba', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Price', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Index', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Manitoba', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Hog', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Manitoba', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Winnipeg', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['West', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Coast', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Vessel', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Loadings', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Canadian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['West', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Coast', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['West', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Coast', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['East', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Coast', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Loading', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Waiting', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Vancouver', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Prince', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['New', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Maritime', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Queen', 'I-MISC', 'I-LOC'], ['Dampier', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Kaohsiung', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['China', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Desk', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Clean', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Danila', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Mobil', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Desk', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Dirty', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Resource', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Ras', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Tanura', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Red', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Mobil', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Lula', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Sidi', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Kreir', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Augusta', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Exxon', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Spetses', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Sidi', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Kreir', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Augusta', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Exxon', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Mesipia', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Bajaia', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Fos', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Exxon', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Euronotes', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Joan', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Wall', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['St', 'I-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Santa', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Homestake', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Wall', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Nevada', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Busang', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Placer', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Dome', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Nevada', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Homestake', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Albuquerque', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Kazakstan', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Ghana', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Homestake', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Longer', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Newmont-Santa', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Fe', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmonth', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Newmont', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Santa', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Fe', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Wall', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Street', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Russ', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Berrie', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Russ', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Berrie', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Maurice', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Kinshasa', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Chapter', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Seven', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Chapter', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Seven', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Kinshasa', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Masisi', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Kisangani', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Medecins', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Goma-Bukavu', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Walikale', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Indian', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Daniella', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Louis', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Central', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['African', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Central', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['African', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Diouf', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Faso', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Moustapha', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['African', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['Bangui', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Faso', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Service', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Yakoma', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Yakomas', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Baya', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Bangui', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Burkina', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Faso', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Mali', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Patasse', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Central', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC'], ['Patasse', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Codos', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Hospital', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['North', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['West', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Russian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Skinheads', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Bratislava', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Rabbi', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Bratislava', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Meyers', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Buza', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Berisha', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Buza', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pope', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Pope', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['John', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pope', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Democratic', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Church', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Nickel', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Rinaco', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Plus', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Livshits', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Nikel', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['City', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Far', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['North', 'O', 'I-LOC'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Krasnoyarsk', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Interrosimpex', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Uneximbank', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Norilsk', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Tallinna', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Tallinna', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Tallinna', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['State', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Russian-U.S.', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Albright', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Warsaw', 'B-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Pact', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Surgeon', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Renat', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Democratic', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Slovakia', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Kazanluk', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Kazanluk', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Ottoman', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Bank', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Sandor', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Jones', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Simec', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Sidek', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Sidek', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Telmex', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Televisa', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Falling', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Brazilians', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Brazilian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Plastic', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Surgery', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Latin', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['America', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Hakme', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Brazilians', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Vice-President', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Oswaldo', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Plastic', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Daily', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Arbitrales', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Quequen', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Rosario', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Bahia', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Blanca', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Oats', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Flint', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Dent', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Sorghum', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Millet', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Buenos', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Aires', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Tampico', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Kenda', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Gulf', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Mexico', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Coast', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Coast', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['California', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Sinaloa', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Baja', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['California', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Sonora', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Gulf', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Mexico', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Tamaulipas', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Gulf', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Quintana', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Roo', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Finance', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Aninat', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Congress', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Congress', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['East', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Timorese', 'I-MISC', 'I-LOC'], ['Nobel', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['East', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Alatas', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Islamic', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Alatas', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Belo', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Belo', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Alatas', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Pope', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Hainan', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Qinglan', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Wenchang', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Rangoon', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['University', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Insein', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Rangoon', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Yangon', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Yangon', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['San', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Suu', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Order', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Restoration', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['League', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['San', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Yangon', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Suu', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Confederation', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Free', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Jordan', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['World', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Trade', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Hansenne', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Jordan', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Jordan', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Southeast', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Asian', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Brunei', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Philippines', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Vietnam', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['India', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Matthew', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Asia', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Rubber', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Markets', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Natural', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Japan', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Finance', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Sakakibara', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Note', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Note', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Union', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Switzerland', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Sakakibara', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Sakakibara', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Mr', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Keizai', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Shimbun', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Toyo', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Haitham', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Haddadin', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['South', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Lebanon', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Lahd', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Etian', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Guardians', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Cedars', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Christian', 'B-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Okla', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Panhandle', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Steers', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Heifers', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Same', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Period', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Same', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Period', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Yearly', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Steer', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Heifer', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Cow', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Bull', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Hartford', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Conn', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['State', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Incorporated', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Jr', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Corrections', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Mohammed', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Prison', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Mills', 'B-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Prison', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Supreme', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Circuit', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Mills', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Lawhon', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Mana', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Iowa-S', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Carcass', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Basis', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Thursdays', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Date', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Man', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Darrel', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Outagmie', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['County', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Circuit', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Court', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Judge', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Luebke', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Voeks', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Voeks', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Statistics', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Canadian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Visible', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Farmers', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Deliveries', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Curr', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Curr', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Date', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Oats', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Barley', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Rye', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Flax', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Curr', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Curr', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Oats', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Barley', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Rye', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Canola', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Oats', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Rye', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Flaxseed', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Canola', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Corn', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Henry', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Hub', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Weather', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Resistance', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Gulf', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Coast', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Hub', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Permian', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Permian', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['East', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['West', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Southwest', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['St.', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Louis', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Merchants', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Exchange', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Chicago', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Trade', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Chicago', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['St.', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Louis', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Toledo', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Corn', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['St.', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Louis', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Toledo', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Oats', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Minneapolis', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Louis', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Toledo', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Chicago', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Action', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Performance', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Ariz', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Action', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Motorsport', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Traditions', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Creative', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Humane', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Society', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Animal', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Hospital', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['American', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Cornwell', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Rottweilers', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Dalmatians', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Doberman', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Rottweilers', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Iowa-S', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Fri-', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Date', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Seller', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Date', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Sm', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Pd', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Wk', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Sm', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Pd', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Basis', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Delivered', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Basis', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Steers', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Basis', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Heifers', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Ghana', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['General', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Niger', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Islamic', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Ghana', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Niger', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['General', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Boutros-Ghali', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['General', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Basque', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Herri', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Batasuna', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Alessandra', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Fascist', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Deputies', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Mussolini', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Loren', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Social', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Duce', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Claus', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Hanover', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Nicholas', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Milan', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Europe', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Agreement', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Bharatiya', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Janata', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Babri', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Ayodhya', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Hindu-Moslem', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Hindus', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Lord', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Rama', 'B-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Petroleum', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Christmas', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Brussels', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Lantau', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Peak', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Hay', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Newcastle', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Kaohsiung', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['China', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Royal', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Clipper', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Maracaibo', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC'], ['Fos', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Coe', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Clerici', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Dampier', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Kaohsiung', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['China', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Conservative', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Conservative', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Treasuries', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bunds', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Saharan', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Blend', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Minas', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Bonny', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Light', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Arabian', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Light', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Dubai', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Tia', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Juana', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Isthmus', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Clarke', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Exchequer', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Clarke', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Newfoundland', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Newfoundland', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Learjet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Snow', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Grand', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Rapids', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['Arafat-Netanyahu', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Palestinian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Abdel-Rahman', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Terrorists', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Kesers', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Kurdistan', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Okla', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Panhandle', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Week', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Holiday', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Date', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Ago', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Slaughter', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Steers', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Pen', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Pen', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Select', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Choice', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Delphis', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Hanover', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Delphis', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Hanover', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Aaa', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Baa', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Northeastern', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['State', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Athens', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Olympic', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Airways', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Pan', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['American', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Rashid', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Abu', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pan', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['American', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Athens', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['High', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['School', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Mexico', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Activities', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Cito', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Western', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Consumer', 'B-PER', 'I-MISC'], ['Project', 'I-PER', 'I-MISC'], ['Berne', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bator', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['America', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Network', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Internet', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Europeans', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Garamba', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Ugandan', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Benchaou', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Mantua', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['League', 'B-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Let', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['League', 'B-LOC', 'I-MISC'], ['Viva', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Italia', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['League', 'B-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Po', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['River', 'O', 'I-LOC'], ['Padania', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Radiometer', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Wednesday', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Soeren', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Antwerp', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Antwerp', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Franc', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['January-August', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Salvador', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Hamburg', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Munich', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Re', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Muenchener', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Rueckversicherungs', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Munich', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Re', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Munich', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Re', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Munich', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Re', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['European', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Brussels', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['John', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Lewis', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Partnership', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Waitrose', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['London', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Timah', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Timah', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Receipt', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Clarke', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Conservative', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Member', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Conservatives', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Cabinet', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Newsnight', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Major', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Pro-European', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Conservative', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Edwina', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Court', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Affairs', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Foreign', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Affairs', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Pamela', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['South', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Wales', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Supreme', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Leszic', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Sydney', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Crofts', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Nats', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['First', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Zealand', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Nat', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Zealand', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Labour', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Labour', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Capital', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Territory', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Halverson', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Labor', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Canberra', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bureau', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Yangon', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Dagon', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Order', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Restoration', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Commerce', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Vessel', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Date', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Arrival', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Quantity', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Destination', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Iran', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Sabr', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Princess', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Loine', 'I-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Philippines', 'B-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Deligst', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Seagramd', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Lucky', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Emdldm', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Algoa', 'B-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Sangthai', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Glory', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['Myos', 'B-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Yang', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Budisuryana', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['King', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Ace', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['Tong', 'B-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Shun', 'I-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Vietnam', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['But', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Bangkok', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Hui', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Bao', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Heavy', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Koram', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Guilin', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Guilin', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Guangxi', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Port', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Office', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['China', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['General', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Guangxi', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Guilin', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Sangetsu', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Sangetsu', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Busang', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Arasu', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Busang', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Mines', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Said', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Busang', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Indonesian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Busang', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Busang', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Ministry', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Ministry', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Bre-X', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Panutan', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Duta', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Group', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Busang', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Group', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Honda', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Motor', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Singapore', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['World', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Trade', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Representative', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Cunha', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Policy', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Kong', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Yam', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Business', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Policy', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Singapore', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Round', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['General', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Agreement', 'I-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Tariffs', 'I-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Trade', 'I-MISC', 'O'], ['Supple', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['West', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Supple', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Singaporean', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Supple', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Singapore', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Nippon', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Telephone', 'I-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Posts', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Telecommunications', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Ahold', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Lumpur', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Johor', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Bahru', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Ahold', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Ahold', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Ahold', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Ahold', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Name', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Age', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Lillehammer', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Winter', 'B-MISC', 'I-PER'], ['Olympics', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Provisional', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Florence', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Stefanie', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Heidi', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Shannon', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Regine', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Megan', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Gerety', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Catherine', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Michaela', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Alexandra', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Ingeborg', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Monika', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Super', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Innisbrook', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Hilton', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Resort', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Tours', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Amateur', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Kelli', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Tiger', 'B-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Beth', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Daniel', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Name', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Renate', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Goetschl', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Age', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Nation', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Lillehammer', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Flachau', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['World', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Europa', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Goetschl', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Downhill', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Markein', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Megan', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Gerety', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Warwara', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Masnada', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Picabo', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Street', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Stefanie', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pace', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Lindsay', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Regine', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Renate', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Carole', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Masnada', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Austria)118', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Claudia', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Sabina', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Stefanie', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Florence', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Madlen', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Katharina', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Miriam', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Marianne', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Nation', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Cup', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Provisional', 'O', 'B-ORG'], ['Gerety', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Florence', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Spela', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pace', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Lindsay', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Bibiana', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Catherine', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Carole', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Brigitte', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Sybille', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Germay', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Grete', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Patrizia', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Alessandra', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Gross', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Belorus', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Renate', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Guenther', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Huber', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Antonio', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Canada', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['La', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Plagne', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Tignes', 'B-LOC', 'O'], ['Dan', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['France', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Veronica', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['States', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Italy', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Huber', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Canada', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['German', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Switzerland', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Germany', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Marco', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Czech', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Republic', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Austria', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Arnold', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Britain', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['United', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['States', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Hines', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Austria', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Kanpur', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Province', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Uttar', 'B-LOC', 'I-PER'], ['Ranji', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Kanpur', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['India-South', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Africa', 'I-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Olivier', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Cooper', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Brenden', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['Bali', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Sun', 'B-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Jun', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Yamakage', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Van', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['British', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Mountain', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Rules', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Kilmarnock', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Winters', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Le', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Tissier', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Southampton', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Villa', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Chelsea', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Sutton', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Ards', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Coleraine', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Linfield', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Pilkington', 'B-MISC', 'B-PER'], ['Bath', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Harlequins', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Irish', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Hartlepool', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Welsh', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Caerphilly', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Llanelli', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Newbridge', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Dunvant', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Bridgend', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Neath', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Boroughmuir', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Millar', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Windass', 'O', 'B-PER'], ['Rangers', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Wallaby', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['South', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Wales', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Super', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Wallaby', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Campese', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Chelsea', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Kanchelskis', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Leicester', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['South', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Thistle', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Premier', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Oxford', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Portsmouth', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['West', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Chesterfield', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Carlisle', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Cardiff', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Derby', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['London', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Efan', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Wimbledon', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['East', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Fife', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Ross', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Forfar', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Thistle', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['City', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Huntly', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Premier', 'B-MISC', 'O'], ['West', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Challenge', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC'], ['Albans', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['United', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Wood', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Town', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Town', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Wallaby', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Wallaby', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Burke', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Burke', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC'], ['Barbarians', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Zimbabwe', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['South', 'B-MISC', 'B-LOC'], ['Whitelaw', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Murless', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Trevor', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Merwe', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Fourie', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Bradford', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Northern', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['World', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Albanian', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Northern', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Regular', 'O', 'B-MISC'], ['Hafizi', 'B-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Belfast', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Sokol', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Prenga', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Sheffield', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Shield', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Tasmania', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Bellerive', 'B-LOC', 'B-PER'], ['Laurie', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Pace', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Sheffield', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Shield', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG'], ['Tasmania', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Victoria', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Tasmania', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Victoria', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Asian', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Asian', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Do', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Sun', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Hong', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Koreans', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Koreans', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Indonesians', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Putra', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Koreans', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Sudiriman', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Sakti', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Do', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Sun', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Hong', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Yehuda', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Tel', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Lezion', 'I-ORG', 'O'], ['Tel', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Yehuda', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Maccabi', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Asian', 'B-MISC', 'B-ORG'], ['Kuwait', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Indonesia', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Do', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['Sun', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Hong', 'I-PER', 'B-LOC'], ['Jeon', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Putra', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Kuwait', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Indonesia', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Basketball', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['Association', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Jersey', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['New', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['York', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Phoenix', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Vancouver', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Charlotte', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Indiana', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Orlando', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['League', 'B-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['National', 'B-ORG', 'I-ORG'], ['League', 'B-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Philadelphia', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['St', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Louis', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG'], ['Ottawa', 'B-LOC', 'B-ORG'], ['Vancouver', 'B-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Pavel', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['League', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC'], ['Bure', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Vancouver', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Buffalo', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Bure', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Galley', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Bure', 'B-PER', 'I-PER'], ['Bure', 'B-PER', 'O'], ['Ottawa', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Axel', 'B-PER', 'I-ORG'], ['Schulz', 'I-PER', 'B-PER'], ['International', 'B-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Federation', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC'], ['Suker', 'I-PER', 'O'], ['New', 'O', 'B-LOC'], ['Year', 'O', 'I-MISC'], ['Christmas', 'O', 'I-PER'], ['Tenerife', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['De', 'B-ORG', 'B-PER'], ['Graafschap', 'I-ORG', 'B-ORG'], ['Doetinchem', 'B-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['The', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Super', 'I-ORG', 'B-MISC'], ['Bilbao', 'I-ORG', 'B-LOC'], ['Vallecano', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Vigo', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER'], ['Espanyol', 'B-ORG', 'O'], ['Gijon', 'O', 'I-ORG'], ['Charlton', 'B-PER', 'B-MISC'], ['Charlton', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Republic', 'B-LOC', 'B-MISC'], ['Ireland', 'I-LOC', 'B-LOC'], ['Charlton', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['Charlton', 'B-PER', 'B-ORG'], ['World', 'I-MISC', 'B-MISC']]